New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 7524 - A 7814 (1947). (Box 33)
  - House of De Rita, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 70)
  - John Reber Baking Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 72)
  - Friedland Fixture Corporation, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 73)
  - Hudson Chromium, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 74)
  - SM Fields and Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 75)
  - Finker, Kornblit, and Braverman, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 76)
  - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 77)
  - American Merrilei Corporation, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 78)
  - Jane Ardsley Shop, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 79)
  - Matam Corp.--Matmatic Division, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 80)
  - Central Wire Frame Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 81)
  - R. Fahey, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 82)
  - Plumbing and Heating Wholesalers Employers Association, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 83)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 84)
  - Crescent Furniture Mfg. Co., Et Al, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 85)
  - Capitol Counter Display Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 86)
  - Metropolitan Roll and Pastry Association, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 87)
  - Pinaud Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 88)
  - Royal Pharmacal Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 89)
  - Strauss Stores Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 90)
  - Menton and Fox Dental Laboratory, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 91)
  - Harry Kazan Linoleum Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 92)
  - George H. Flinn Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 93)
  - Janaug Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 94)
  - Joy Meat Market, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 95)
  - Stanley Plastics Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 96)
  - Uptown Dental Labs, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Waldes Koh-I-Noor, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 98)
  - Laurem Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 99)
  - GM Co. Mfg., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 100)
  - Oxford Pants Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 101)
- A 7815 - A 8208 (1947). (Box 34)
  - Atta Boy Wash Suit Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Coh-Ler Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Tissue Products Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Electro Physical Labs, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Namm Store, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Schwabb Rubber Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Antipyros Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Larkin Electro Products Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Gloka Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Union News Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - ABC Wire, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Reliable Optical Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Cooper's Radio and Sport Shop, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Furniture Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Midtown realty Owners Association, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Realty Advisory Board On Labor Relations, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Westerman Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Durkee Famous Foods, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Embassy Restaurant, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - J. Marcus and Company, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Associated Foundries and Manufacturers, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Schnur Bakery, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Rose Frame and Mirror Works Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Yonkers Bus Company, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Patek Manufacturing Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - 710 St. Anns Ave. Et Al, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Strauss Stores Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Hall Anderson Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Ketchum Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Oralcraft DL and union Square DL, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Parke Davis and Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Pur-al Paint, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Swiss American Watch Hospital, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Waldes Koh-I-Noor, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Bushwick Optical Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Lasko Strap Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Namm Store, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Huron Stevedoring Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Standard brands Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - De Nobili Cigar Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - AG Spalding and Bros., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - City Paint Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - 1365 Sheridan Ave. Et Al, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - David Schwartz Dental Laboratory, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Christ Cell, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Euclid Hall Residence Club, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Hawley and Hoops Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - New Process Mills Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Morris Best, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - J Horne Furniture Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - United Parcel Service, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Becker Bros. Engraving Co., Et Al, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Childs Co, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Friedland Fixture Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Albemarle Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Mayo Et Al, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Bee Lines, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Otto Guggenheim, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - WS Wilson Corp, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - United Whelan Cigar Stores Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Fink Baking Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Hudson-American Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - WS Wilson Corp, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Borden's Farm Products, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - ME Stern and Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Zilinski and Sternberg Dental Lab, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Bryant Pharmacy, Et Al, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Gilmore Steak House, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Precision Woodcraft Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Philip Sievering, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Wintermeier's Bakeries, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Monmouth Products, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - GM Co. Mfg., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Gloka Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Shipman Stationary, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Hercules Food Equipment, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - Chain Furniture Shops, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Reubens Restaurant, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - Union News Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - Oxford Pants Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - Vogue Novelty Jewelry Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - Dew Drug Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - Janaug Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - Oxford Handkerchief Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - Supreme Knitting Machine Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - National Automotive Parts Association, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 88)
  - National Exhibition Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 89)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 90)
  - K. Stenzel and Sons, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 91)
  - Hiram Walker Distributors, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 92)
  - Bronze Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 93)
  - 1561-71 Sheridan Ave, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 94)
  - Hercules Food Service Equipment, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 95)
  - Le Cody Toasted Pie Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 96)
  - Metro Window and Ceiling Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 97)
  - Namms Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 98)
  - New York Subway Advertising Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 99)
  - Julius Pollak and Sons, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 100)
  - Leo L. Eichen, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 101)
  - 1855 7th Ave, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 102)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers Int'l, Local 1, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 103)
  - Boys and Mens Shop, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 104)
  - Coldwell-Philadelphia Lawn Mower Division of Portable Products Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 105)
  - Eastern Novelty Mirror Manufacturers Association, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 106)
  - Henry Modell and Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 107)
  - HK Metalcraft Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 108)
  - Marc Seyden, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 109)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 110)
  - US Metal Products, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 111)
  - Queens Bifocal Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 112)
  - Associated Fur Processors, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 113)
  - Greenberg Brothers, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 114)
  - Metro Soft Drink Board of Trade, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 115)
  - Shellcraft Optical Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 116)
  - Tru-Line Die Co, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 117)
  - Childs Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 118)
  - RH Macy and Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 119)
  - Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 120)
  - Lee Spring Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 121)
  - Bush Terminal Buildings Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 122)
  - Goro Mfg. Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 123)
  - Hilton Tool and Machine, Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 124)
  - Lerick and Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 125)
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Co., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 126)
  - filler (Box 34, Folder 127)
- A 8209 - A 8646 (1947-48). (Box 35)
  - 2325 Rye Avenue, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Ardee Plastics Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - F. Roma and Bros., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - A. De Pinna and Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Le Art, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Baltic Metal Products, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Delta Heating Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Epiphone, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - JL Green, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Seligman and Latz, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Springmaster, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Koler Cigar Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Curtain Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - 39-75 5th Street, Woodside, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Brandoff Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Mye Drug Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - 825-1146 Colgate Avenue, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - 333 Warburton Avenue, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - 8259-1665 Weeks Ave, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - 2160 Holland Ave, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - 2600 Creston Ave., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - 3422 Knox Place, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Pulaski Trucking Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - D.I. Brass Turning Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - 8278 Ward Baking Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Waldes Koh-I-Nor, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Charles and Carl Silverstein Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Joseph Franks and Sons, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Emil Koudelka, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Alpine Knitting and Glove Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - American Spring Corp, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Keys Orthopedic Shoe Research Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - World Store Equipment, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - 1411-23 Avenue N, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Newport Optical Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Dash Metal Products Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Good Humor Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Borden's Farm Products Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - National Suit and Coat Industry Recovery Board, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Whitelawn Dairies Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Ace Sample card Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - De Nobilli Cigar Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Spear and Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Strauss Fasteners Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - 1704 East 15th St., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Style Metal Specialties Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - 37-30 74th Street, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Ace Novelty Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Gloka Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Clarendon Hotel, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - LA Social Cigar Corp, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Townley's Restaurant, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Continental Chair Frame Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Bernard Fels, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - SM Fields and Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - C. Greenbaum and Son, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Kozan's Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - JA Maurer and Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Photographic Studio Employers Association of NY, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Royal Woodcraft Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Solar Furniture Contracting Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Charles IH Greenbaum, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - J. Michaels and Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - 1594 East New York Ave., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Bright Chair Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Mallin Furniture Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Purity Bakeries Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Singer Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - 2810 Olinville Avenue, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Abbott Appliance and Music Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Modern Workshop, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Sonotone Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - 8015-8020 Bay Parkway, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Ronzoni Macaroni Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - F and S Die Cutting Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - J Blatt Picture Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Elliot Cheesman Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Ferro-Co Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - New York Pressing Machinery Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Geo V. Clark Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - Progressive Restaurant Owners Assn., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - Allied Maintenance Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 82)
  - Oakbrook Furniture Co., Et Al, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - Joseph Lerner and Sons, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - Mark Can Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - Ward Baking Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - Saymont Optical Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 87)
  - Baltic Metal Products Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 88)
  - J. Gold Dental Laboratory, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 89)
  - Schwab Bros and Baer Cigar Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 90)
  - 2021 Grand Concourse, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 91)
  - Circle Wire and Cable Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 92)
  - Strauss Brothers and Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 93)
  - Elexa Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 94)
  - 701 Avenue C, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 95)
  - Globe Electronics, Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 96)
  - Harjer Furniture Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 97)
  - Jimmie's Chop House, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 98)
  - Manhattan Wire Goods Co., Et Al, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 99)
  - Advance Button and Buckle, Et Al, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 100)
  - Apex Oil Burner Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 101)
  - Doughnut Corporation of America, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 102)
  - General Bronze Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 103)
  - George J. Schwarz, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - Namm's Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 105)
  - Williamsburg Lumber Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 106)
  - Wellmade Parlor Frame Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 107)
  - Flatbush Window Cleaning Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 108)
  - Union News Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 109)
  - 2518 Webb Avenue, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 110)
  - Empire Wire Goods Co., Et Al, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 111)
  - Whitlock Corp., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 112)
  - Montauk Mfg. Co, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 113)
  - Superior Meter Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 114)
  - John Chatillon and Sons, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 115)
  - CJ Tagliabue Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 116)
  - Gottfried Banking Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 117)
  - Port Chester Iron Works Inc., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 118)
  - Guide System and Supply Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 119)
  - Hilton Tool and Machine Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 120)
  - Singer Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 35, Folder 121)
  - 2066 Morris Ave., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 122)
  - American Mica Works, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 123)
  - Adams Engineering Co., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 124)
  - J. Zonon, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 125)
  - Abbot Appliance and Music Co., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 126)
  - National Silver Deposit ware Co., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 127)
  - 37-30 74th Street, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 128)
  - 1104 Manor Ave, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 129)
  - Gimbel Bros. Inc., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 130)
- A 8648 - A 9099 (1948). (Box 36)
  - Allied Molding Corp, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Haddasah, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Food Crest Restaurant, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Rose and Goldstein, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Reichhold Chemical Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - American Die Cutting Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - American Mica Works, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co. of NY, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Irene's Millinery, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Shunt Lamp Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Clayton's Department Store, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Ford Instrument Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Gotham Furniture Frame Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Milo Radio and Electronics Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Travers Pharmacy, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - St. Mary's Street, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - 1230 Sheridan Ave., et al, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Grand Concourse, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - 1869 Walton Ave., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Joe Lowe Corp, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - American Zyloptic Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Meadow Gold Products Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Nelson Brothers, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - New York Mounters Assn., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Autocar Sales and Service Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - RK Baking Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Wire Products Manufacturers Assn., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - New York Central Building, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Pechter Baking Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Supreme Metal Fabricators, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - JS Mill Supply Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Childs Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - 2198 Cruger Ave., et al, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Spear and Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Zito Bakery, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Carolina Box Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Keller Dorian Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Joe Lowe Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Morey machinery Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - 853 East 170 Street, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Four Star Pharmacy, Luncheonette, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Phoenix Pharmacy, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Lou Seidman and Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - J Michaels and Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Allan Oxygen Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Sunshine Biscuit Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - 602 St. Mary's Street, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Coronet Silverplate Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Kozy Footwear Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Lawyers Title Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Whitelawn Dairies, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Ace Drug Luncheonette, et al, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Brooks Furniture Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Coldwell-Philadelphia Lawn Mower Div. of Portable Products Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Nu-Art Upholstery Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Pioneer Mounting and Finishing Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - M. Millman and Sons, Furniture Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Warner News, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Wilson and Rogers, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Euclid Hall, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - Hotel Jefferson, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - Hotel Standish Hall, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - Irving Arms, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - HC Bohack and Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - Kings Electronics Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - Perfect Upholstery Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - Joseph Stein et al., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  - Chas Fischer Spring Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 74)
  - Hercules Electric Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 75)
  - Dugan Brothers, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 76)
  - Schwab Rubber Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 77)
  - Lawyers Title Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 78)
  - Modern Upholstering Comfort Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 79)
  - Seligman and Latz, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 80)
  - Emery Thompson Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 81)
  - 873 Freeman Street, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 82)
  - 3075 Heath Ave., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 83)
  - Hyde Park Hotel, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 84)
  - 7825 Fourth Avenue, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 85)
  - Epiphone Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 86)
  - 1015 Liggett Ave. et al, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 87)
  - 1235 GR Concourse et al, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 88)
  - 1765 Davidson Ave, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 89)
  - Sam Biern, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 90)
  - Gottfried Banking Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 91)
  - Mansfield Furniture Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 92)
  - Sound Furniture Mfg. Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 93)
  - Unites States Lines Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 94)
  - 555-557 Timpson Place, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 95)
  - Nemirow Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 96)
  - JB Salterini Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 97)
  - 2235 Bassford Ave, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 98)
  - Van Dorn Baking Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 99)
  - Peerless Art Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 100)
  - Weavecraft Fabrics, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 101)
  - Amity Dyeing and Finishing Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 102)
  - Hall Anderson Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 103)
  - Manhattan School of Dental Technicians, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 104)
  - Peerless Machine and Tool Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 105)
  - Avon Upholstering Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 106)
  - Paramount Upholstery Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 107)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 108)
  - Modecraft Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 109)
  - Pollak, Julius, and Sons, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 110)
  - Home Bedspring Mfg. Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 111)
  - 2180 Wallace Avenue, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 112)
  - Bergen Bed Spring Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 114)
  - General Window Display Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 115)
  - Grosso Bakery, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 116)
  - F. Roma and Bros, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 117)
  - X-L Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 118)
  - 950 St. John Ave, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 119)
  - 1869 Bathgate Ave., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 120)
  - Louis H. Kosh and Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 121)
  - New York Rubber Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 122)
  - Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 123)
  - Purity Bakeries Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 124)
  - Robert Louis Stevenson High School, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 125)
  - 1681 49 Street, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 126)
  - Adept Mercantile Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 127)
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 128)
  - Farmacia Blanco, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 129)
  - Kant Amusement Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 130)
  - J. Marcus Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 131)
  - Workmen's Circle, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 132)
  - 1514 West 8th Street, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 133)
  - Epiphone, Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 134)
  - JB Salterini Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 135)
  - Wagner Baking Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 136)
  - General Bronze Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 137)
  - Eastern Wine Corp., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 138)
  - Metro Sacks Co., 1948 (Box 36, Folder 139)
  - Filler (Box 36, Folder 140)
- A 9101 - A 9499 (1948). (Box 37)
  - Laurel Dept. Stores, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Otto Guggenheim and Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - HM Stevens Caterers, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 2735 Sedgwick Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 1916 Grand Concourse, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Standard Bag Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Gilmore's Steak House, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Madam Corp., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Miroflex Productions Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Warner Bros. Circuit, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Fleetwood Banking Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Dash Metal Products Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - 4515 12th Avenue, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Amity Plastics, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - 387 South 5th Street, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Ford Instrument Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - 616 E. Lincoln Ave., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - 2120 Harrison St., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Berchofsky Bros., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Bluestein's Baby Carriage Mfg. Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Eton Chemists, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Gripsholm Restaurant, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Linden Parlor Frame Co., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Majestic Chair Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 37, Folder 24)